(Penny:)Cheers!
(Bernadette:)Emily, what do you do?
(Emily:)I'm a dermatology resident
at Huntington Hospital.
(Raj:)And you know what that means.
(Raj:)Someone's skin's about
to be softer than ever.
(Emily:)This is making me crazy.
I know I know you from somewhere.
(Raj:)Howard was an astronaut.
Maybe that's where you saw him.
(Emily:)Wow, that's amazing.
What was that like?
(Howard:)It was the most incredible
experience of my life.
(Howard:)Up there
in the space station, you're...
(Emily:)Oh, my God, I remember.
(Howard:)Can I finish my astronaut story?
(Emily:)It was four years ago.
(Howard:)-Please don't say it.
-We were set up on a blind date.
-You came to my apartment.
(Howard:)You're saying it.
Well, what happened?
(Bernadette:)-Yeah, what happened?
-OK, I'll say it.
(Howard:)I was on the way to pick her up.
(Howard:)My stomach felt a little funny.
(Howard:)When I got there, I asked
if I could use her bathroom.
(Howard:)Please don't say it.